

somerville MA 02143 ron@0xadada.pub github.com/0xadada @0xADADA

seventeen-plus years professional engineering experience. deep expertise and intuition in multiple technology stacks. independently design and implement systems given loose requirements with goals. mentor other engineers.

create functional, well-tested, maintainable web software. enjoy building highly available, concurrent web applications using open source software. advocate of privacy, open web standards, and security. speaks and writes about humane design, surveillance, philosophy, and cryptocurrencies.

EXPERIENCE

- 2018- Salsify ------ Boston MA web application architecture and implementation, product dev, leadership.
- 2018- Unredacted Word ------ Cambridge MA author, editing, publishing, retail sales (books), marketing.
- 2016-2018 Cinch Financial ------ Boston MA web application architecture and implementation, automation, speaking.
- 2012-2016 Nara Logics ------ Cambridge MA strategy, architecture and implementation, security, automation, mentor.
- 2004-2016 Visual Assault ------ Cambridge MA founder, client services, implementation, UX, race car driving.
- 2011-2012 Boston Interactive ------ Boston MA client services, software implementation, mentor.
- 2009-2011 Cambridge BioMarketing ----- Cambridge MA client services, software implementation.
- 2007-2009 RDVO, Inc ------ Somerville MA software implementation, open web standards evangelism.
- 2007 n2N Commerce ----- Cambridge MA software implementation, testing.
- 2003-2007 HP (Autonomy) ------ Cambridge MA software implementation, testing, network administration.
- 2000-2002 Cyber Access, Rovia Inc, Dell (EMC) ----- Greater Boston MA testing, network administration.

EDUCATION

2015 MAS.S65 Blockchain Technologies ------ MIT Media Lab 2004 BS Computer Science & Cognitive Psychology ----- Northeastern University